MovieID,MovieName,ReleaseDate,Plot,Poster,ProducerID
1,Game of Thrones S1-S8,2019-04-14,Story of ice and fire,0,1
3,Knight and Day,2010-07-09,June Havens meets Roy Miller, a lethal operative, in an unlikely encounter. She gets entangled in his adventures and falls in love with him. But June has to figure out if he's a traitor or a good guy.,0,2
4,Rumble in the Brox,1994-06-23,Please fill the plot,0,3
5,The Medallion,2004-01-24,Please fill the plot,0,3
6,Police Story 1,2003-02-18,pelease fill the plot,0,3
8,Drunken Master,1991-01-17,Please fill the plot,0,3
